A Guide to the Papers of John Staige Davis
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of John Staige Davis
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
3247
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was deposited on 1949 June 30.
Contents List: Papers of John Staige Davis
- Correspondence of John Staige Davis, Sr. 1840-1885, 6 folders (Box 1)
- Medical Papers of John Staige Davis, Sr. n.d (Box 1)
- Correspondence of John Staige Davis n.d., 3 folders (Box 2)
- Correspondence 1867-1888 (Box 2)
- Correspondence 1889-1891 (Box 2)
- Correspondence 1892-1903 (Box 2)
- Correspondence 1903-1904, 4 folders (Box 2)
- Correspondence 1903-1904, 6 folders (Box 3)
- Correspondence 1905-1906, 3 folders (Box 3)
- Correspondence 1905-1906, 5 folders (Box 4)
- Howard Taft to John Staige Davis 1905 Nov 27 (Box 4)
- Correspondence 1907-1908, 2 folders (Box 4)
- Correspondence 1907-1908, 7 folders (Box 5)
- Correspondence 1907-1908 (Box 6)
- Correspondence 1909-1910, 5 folders (Box 6)
- Correspondence 1909-1910, 8 folders (Box 7)
- Correspondence 1911-1912, 6 folders (Box 8)
- Correspondence 1911-1912, 6 folders (Box 9)
- Correspondence 1913-1914, 7 folders (Box 10)
- Correspondence 1913-1914, 5 folders (Box 11)
- Correspondence 1913-1914 (Box 12)
- Correspondence 1915-1916, 4 folders (Box 12)
- Correspondence 1915-1916, 6 folders (Box 13)
- Correspondence 1917-1923 (Box 14)
- Correspondence 1924-1927 (Box 14)
- Correspondence: Post Cards n.d., 1888-1910 (Box 14)
- Correspondence: Post Cards 1911-1924 (Box 14)
- Correspondence: Telegrams 1901-1916 (Box 14)
- Correspondence: T. Duckett Jones 1926-1927 (Box 14)
- Advertisements 1874-1915
- Blank Forms n.d. (Box 14)
- Charts, n.d. (Box 14)
- Consultations n.d., 1906-1915 (Box 15)
- Consultations 1916-1923, 5 folders (Box 15)
- Consultations 1924-1927 (Box 16)
- Correspondence: Medical 1898-1919 (Box 16)
- Correspondence: Medical 1920-1926 (Box 16)
- Exams 1901-1916 (Box 16)
- Miscellanea, n.d. (Box 16)
- Miscellanea n.d.-1924 (Box 16)
- Physical Exams and Personal Histories 1920-1927 Jun, 5 folders (Box 17)
- Physical Exams and Personal Histories 1927-1929 (Box 18)
- Prescriptions n.d. (Box 18)
- Review Notes: A-Z n.d. (Box 18)
- Speeches and Other Papers: A-Z n.d., 3 folders (Box 19)
- X-Ray 1920 (Box 19)
- Certificates and Diplomas of John Staige Davis 1884-1920 (Box 20)
- Financial: Account Books 1860-1867, 1870-1874 (Box 20)
- Financial Papers 1885-1909 (Box 20)
- Financial Papers 1910-1929 (Box 20)
- Legal Papers 1885-1922 (Box 20)
- Memoranda n.d. (Box 20)
- Memoranda 1898-1927 (Box 20)
- Newspaper Clippings 1920-1925 (Box 20)
- Photographs n.d. (Box 20)
- Photographs 1891, 1914, 1944, n.d (Box 21)
- Photographs n.d. (Box 21)
- School Reports 1911, 1914 (Box 21)
- Social 1885-1896 (Box 21)
- University of Virginia n.d., 1867-1932 (Box 21)
- Notebooks (13) n.d. (Box 22)
- Notebooks (2) n.d. (Box 23)
- Boxes of Slides n.d., (2) (Box 23)
- Notebooks (20) n.d. (Box 24)
- Notebooks (13) n.d. (Box 25)
- Notebooks (17) n.d. (Box 26)
- Notebooks (8) n.d. (Box 27)
- Notebooks (4) n.d. (Box 28)
- Diplomas from the University of Virginia for John Staige Davis: French Language and Literature; Latin Language and Literature; and, Spanish Language and Literature 1839 Jul 4 (Oversize Box P-21)
- Appointment of John Staige Davis to the National Conference of Charities and Correction from the Commonwealth of Virginia, signed by Governor Claude A. Swann 1908 Apr 15 (Oversize Box P-21)
- Review Examinations on Anatomy: notes on surgical anatomy and the nervous system n.d. (Oversize P-21)